tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:1", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-001 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall be implemented at End State to support the Fortescue 2030 Real Zero target.", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA196.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5274", "0", "", "Class0","{B38D43B2-9680-492a-88BC-5249BDD112E2}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:2", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-002 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall maintain 192 Mtpa of annual tonnage", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA197.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5275", "0", "", "Class0","{C9B74AD0-85A6-4403-8D30-C48B892B9A07}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:3", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-003 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall enable Current System service levels of 24 hours per day, 7 days per week, 365 days per year.", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA198.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5276", "0", "", "Class0","{32982F99-724D-4fc5-88EF-2FF248792E94}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:4", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-005 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall support Sprint Running at the level provided by the Current System", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA199.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5347", "0", "", "Class0","{FB52746E-143A-49f6-9265-3DF2EB4380A9}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:5", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-009 The Battery Electric Locomotives shall possess a Kinematic Envelope that ensures entering and traversing through rail infrastructure is free of hindrance with any structure, equipment or fitting.", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA200.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5345", "0", "", "Class0","{6EE0EBC2-06DE-4297-88ED-B36638F5A15F}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:6", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-010 Track shall support the increased weight and performance profile of Battery Electric Locomotives in Normal, Abnormal, Degraded and Emergency Mode operation.", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA201.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5346", "0", "", "Class0","{B090089A-6F37-47b2-9B8F-E175BE3D4CBB}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:7", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-012 All signals shall be sighted for the battery electric locomotives (BEL).", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA202.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E6581", "0", "", "Class0","{D5DD8133-18ED-43e8-8B76-A0F729CE1651}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:8", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-015 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall accommodate peak stabling demands during the transfer from Diesel Locomotives to BEL vehicles.", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA203.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5341", "0", "", "Class0","{E7FCB40A-CF0B-4a9c-8344-AADAD1B7BA71}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:9", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-016 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall provide Rollingstock Maintenance facilities that are configurable to accommodate Hybrid Operations", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA204.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5342", "0", "", "Class0","{A6DAAB56-3FA0-418b-B5EB-6E16AC77BF83}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:10", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-017 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall provide Train Arrestors suitable for the Battery Electric Locomotives", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA205.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5343", "0", "", "Class0","{7530B2E2-C199-4316-8B10-4E8776563188}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:11", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-018 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall accommodate projected future freight fleet increase.", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA206.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5344", "0", "", "Class0","{33B48CA5-BFB1-4c01-BAFB-2F3874CC9A43}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:12", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-022 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall ensure BEL vehicles interface with existing Ore Cars", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA207.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5336", "0", "", "Class0","{FA164DD4-FC8F-44b1-903E-257C20F02B21}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:13", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-023 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall ensure BEL vehicles interface with the existing DEL vehicles", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA208.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5337", "0", "", "Class0","{206991C1-B2E4-40ee-AD8F-73D4A2FD8616}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:14", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-024 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall ensure Traction Power provision supports BEL power demand characteristics", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA209.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5338", "0", "", "Class0","{CA79938C-8B9C-4d3e-98CE-A7ABAD828919}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:15", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-025 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall ensure Overhead Line Equipment provision supports BEL power demand characteristics", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA210.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5339", "0", "", "Class0","{DECCE14F-5F8C-4431-93AD-5E73C8E17D17}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:16", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-026 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall not impart Power Imbalance to the Rail Network", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA211.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5340", "0", "", "Class0","{AA686D4A-E7C3-436c-9462-1E701A8EF48E}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:17", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-036 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall provide Rollingstock Maintenance Facilities that maintain BEL vehicles", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA212.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5317", "0", "", "Class0","{E7FBD4AE-7AC7-4348-AA23-BFAF51F49A5C}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:18", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-037 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall enable the perparation of newly arrived BEL in designated stabling locations", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA213.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5318", "0", "", "Class0","{F480DC5D-C105-4805-B378-1436AAFDB164}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:19", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-038 The Rail Decarbonisation System Rollingstock Maintenance facilities shall be sized to provide required maintenance capability during both the Hybrid Operation and BEL End State", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA214.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5319", "0", "", "Class0","{28F66928-B48E-4911-98E9-9F039C6BA3EF}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:20", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-039 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall allow for the safe interaction and disposal of hazardous materials related to BEL and Battery Tender vehicle maintenance", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA215.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5320", "0", "", "Class0","{7E04FC15-683A-4ec4-96F1-1A778A1DAEF3}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:21", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-040 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall provide safe access to the Track for maintenance", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA216.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5321", "0", "", "Class0","{695EAFC5-D477-4b30-A381-0F602D922ACE}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:22", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-041 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall provide safe access to the Trackside Equipment for maintenance", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA217.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5322", "0", "", "Class0","{F2E5171B-4CE8-4e37-A04A-A788CA4BC1BC}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:23", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-042 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall ensure suitable levels of operator accommodation is available to operate Diesel Locomotives and BELs during the Hybrid Operation phase", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA218.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5323", "0", "", "Class0","{3900D9CF-23F3-4950-8901-B74900B40414}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:24", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-043 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall provide training facilites for Nominated Staff supporting BEL migration demand and catering for the appropriate skill level and competency management requirements", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA219.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5324", "0", "", "Class0","{F6EA3ADF-94DE-40c4-9909-2F1C84EFE940}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:25", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-044 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall assess and identify the changes needed to current operational rules and procedures for the Fortescue rail network and all other impacted interfacing systems", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA220.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5325", "0", "", "Class0","{F202033D-52CB-4943-8527-EC31D13CC123}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:26", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-045 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall assess and identify the changes needed to current Maintenance Procedures", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA221.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5326", "0", "", "Class0","{15265E56-4C43-40e9-90A1-FD7D5C2ECDF7}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:27", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-046 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall ensure training needs analysis are carried out to support future BEL migration demand", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA222.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5327", "0", "", "Class0","{6F0A5A61-17CE-49a8-96F1-29C384715465}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:28", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-047 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall produce rules and procedures for Normal Mode, Abnormal Mode, Degraded Mode operations and Emergency Mode operations", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA223.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5328", "0", "", "Class0","{6D1D2542-A236-4f19-A3AB-82EE48DFF022}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:29", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-048 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall ensure Nominated Staff required to operate the system are trainined to the appropriate skill levels", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA224.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5329", "0", "", "Class0","{D9C2E47D-FB0B-4454-AE82-B0BEED460D38}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:30", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-049 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall ensure Nominated Staff required to maintain the system are trainined to the appropriate skill levels", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA225.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5330", "0", "", "Class0","{A384581A-6FA5-4f40-B135-5B1113CFC5AB}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:31", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-050 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall ensure sufficient numbers of trainined competent Nominated Staff are available to operate and maintain the Rail Decarbonisation System through the Hybrid Operation.", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA226.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5331", "0", "", "Class0","{94DE362E-ED02-43c8-B851-1AC358EB4EBF}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:32", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-051 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall enable Nominated Staff to perform competently during Normal, Abnormal, Degraded and Emergency operating conditions", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA227.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5332", "0", "", "Class0","{0B97258E-4382-4494-8BDF-07853B3A007D}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:33", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-052 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall enable Nominated Staff to perform Maintenance activities competently", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA228.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5333", "0", "", "Class0","{B220E508-1DF5-4b69-87D1-FA48C2A666D3}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:34", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-053 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall enable Nominated Staff to perform Operation activities competently", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA229.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5334", "0", "", "Class0","{C121A26D-0CB6-42cd-AA40-98FB8FAAC4F3}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:35", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-054 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall provide the capability for Nominated Staff and required equipment to access required areas to perform Operation activities", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA230.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5335", "0", "", "Class0","{75B166EC-46CD-4e8c-B275-45888A552FF4}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:36", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-062 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall maintain or improve Current System Level Crossing Safety Risks", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA231.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5310", "0", "", "Class0","{92865DA4-929C-4085-BA09-ED094F95A362}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:37", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-063 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall not increase the number of Line of Fire Events", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA232.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5311", "0", "", "Class0","{D98C2A6A-6F0E-499e-B714-7C9C17C312CB}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:38", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-064 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall provide information required to update the Fortescue Safety Management System", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA233.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5312", "0", "", "Class0","{FA367F1F-6543-45e2-A2ED-560D81399F6D}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:39", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-065 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall provide a high level of Availability to ensure 192 Mtpa annual tonnage is achieved, with the specific percentage target to be determined during the System Definition phase based on operational needs and...", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA234.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5313", "0", "", "Class0","{6D6C6D3F-2233-4442-86A8-555B7870DB4E}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:40", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-066 The Rail Decarbonisation System implementation and End State shall be configured to minimise need for service disrupting possessions", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA235.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5314", "0", "", "Class0","{F81C3F91-DB2B-43e9-8D80-9E17880DDB50}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:41", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-067 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall maintain or improve Current System recovery time from Incidents", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA236.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5315", "0", "", "Class0","{5170D882-408F-4ac5-885E-852A295DFEE1}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:42", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-068 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall not increase the frequency of out of service locomotives per equivalent annual tonnage", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA237.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5316", "0", "", "Class0","{223CB6B0-86E4-47c5-91AF-D681B2D86977}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:43", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-071 The Rail Decarbonisation System enabling technology shall be supportable over the lifetime of the system", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA238.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5308", "0", "", "Class0","{9C6FF38B-D4F3-43be-B8F0-00D169C3FC0B}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:44", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-072 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall not impact the functionality and operability of the TLO and TUL operations", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA239.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5309", "0", "", "Class0","{2674A499-56C7-4a93-886F-95982ECB6759}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:45", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-077 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall be protected such that neither software nor any introduced asset to the Rail Decarbonisation System can be accessed or tampered with by unauthorised persons, devices or materials", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA240.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5307", "0", "", "Class0","{EF2F1764-2FDD-484b-8ED9-E9CA324E5D77}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:46", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-085 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall define a commercialisation strategy for the RDP solution, outlining the steps for scaling and market adoption.", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA241.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E6578", "0", "", "Class0","{B41E51DF-7BDF-4bb7-8174-5EA69D6BCF44}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:47", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-086 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall mitigate risks to Indigenous heritage areas by implementing an Indigenous Heritage Consultation process, ensuring compliance with relevant heritage protection laws and integrating stakeholder input...<br />", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA242.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E6579", "0", "", "Class0","{E913A451-887D-479b-9064-6FFA9C671EBB}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:48", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-087 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall remain within the Snap Back Boundary", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA243.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E6585", "0", "", "Class0","{F7CE48AB-9EFC-49a1-9489-02B6A09A64DB}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:49", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-088 The Rail Decarbonisation System&#39;s modifications to level crossings shall maintain or enhance cycle time operational efficiency, ensuring no increase in transit delays or reduction in network performance.", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA244.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E6580", "0", "", "Class0","{70D84454-F88B-4674-B371-CB727C5ABC0F}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:50", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-089 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall rationalise the usage and introduction of applications by consolidating or eliminating redundancies, ensuring no increase in system response times.", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA245.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E6584", "0", "", "Class0","{7DA534B8-D4B8-446b-B209-CB7171F4A2BA}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:51", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-090 The Rail Decarbonisation System control/comms equipment shall have a Design Life of 15 years.", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA246.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E6638", "0", "", "Class0","{F24B7420-7E0A-4867-805B-ACA611D02A70}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:52", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-091 The Rail Decarbonisation System power electronics equipment shall have a Design Life of 25 years.", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA247.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E6639", "0", "", "Class0","{6A3E499F-8386-4e64-8845-3A9456A8B74A}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:53", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-092 The Rail Decarbonisation System switchgear shall have a Design Life of 30 years.", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA248.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E6640", "0", "", "Class0","{0E2882B0-699E-416c-92DF-DB93C5B84744}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:54", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-093 The Rail Decarbonisation System transformers shall have a Design Life of 40 years.", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA249.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E6641", "0", "", "Class0","{2241BE2C-87FD-40c9-887A-EC231CE85C88}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:55", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-094 The Rail Decarbonisation System low voltage equipment shall have a Design Life of 25.", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA250.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E6642", "0", "", "Class0","{219D8C03-A35D-49ea-8D29-E33A5F633022}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:56", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-004 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall not require an increase in rakes to maintain operational capacity", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA251.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5173", "0", "", "Class0","{4F8826EF-AE1A-40e3-A1A5-0952DD3D29CF}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:57", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-006 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall incorporate the use of Battery Electric Locomotives to achieve the system decarbonisation target", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA252.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5174", "0", "", "Class0","{EA4D00DE-A3A4-40c9-8620-5FB536E46135}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:58", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-007 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall incorporate Dynamic Charging", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA253.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5175", "0", "", "Class0","{2CADAF1E-7240-42e0-A406-23EE5530ED2D}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:59", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-008 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall incorporate Static Charging", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA254.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5176", "0", "", "Class0","{ACE7016F-0923-43ab-B1B0-2255B4DEDA83}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:60", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-011 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall prevent Battery Electric Locomotives from being routed into network sections which are not enabled for the characteristics of the train", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA255.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5177", "0", "", "Class0","{B3A23F07-8231-47cf-8814-AC75F8B81AFC}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:61", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-013 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall support disaster recovery of BEL vehicle consists", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA256.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5180", "0", "", "Class0","{24D55D14-0E09-4437-BBD1-54B97557812F}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:62", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-014 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall provide Rolling Stock Maintenance Facilities that accommodate BEL vehicles", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA257.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5181", "0", "", "Class0","{56DB1AAB-73EC-4d59-89B9-6E6EC7D56110}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:63", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-019 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall support the inter-running of Battery Electric Locomotives and Diesel Locomotives", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA258.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5182", "0", "", "Class0","{C4F40F7C-AC45-4f73-9FAF-8B5CC8F7A684}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:64", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-020 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall be configured to permit the safe passage of non-BEL vehicles within all interfacing areas", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA259.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5183", "0", "", "Class0","{9AE7C609-3BCD-48aa-927C-A9AEFDFEF578}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:65", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-021 During the Hybrid Operation, the Rail Decarbonisation System shall not increase Current System levels of risk", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA260.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5184", "0", "", "Class0","{28311177-2C40-42f3-B270-8BD91D7D106E}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:66", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-027 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall provide Near Real-Time data for use by Green Supply to assist in the modelling of Rail Network energy consumption and demand", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA261.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5186", "0", "", "Class0","{DBE6B77A-9732-4a9a-A049-174D41B1C1D2}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:67", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-028 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall provide train control appropriate for the BEL, to facilitate controlled operation over all specified scheduled routes", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA262.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5187", "0", "", "Class0","{226C9BB5-3209-4114-AE01-EAE56CA4BB26}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:68", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-029 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall enable remote monitoring of BEL Battery Health via the Train Control System", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA263.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5189", "0", "", "Class0","{18007440-C219-41e0-8DDF-17D0AA5338DD}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:69", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-030 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall provide remote health monitoring, diagnostics, and event recording in support of failure rectification, preventative maintenance, incident investigation", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA264.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5190", "0", "", "Class0","{797FFDC8-3257-4e90-81A0-F580B82555E6}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:70", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-031 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall enable remote monitoring of BEL Battery Energy Consumption via the Fortescue Hive", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA265.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5191", "0", "", "Class0","{92F42374-0DD6-4d15-AAC0-5C4875E378B1}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:71", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-032 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall capture and record battery Performance Data", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA266.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5192", "0", "", "Class0","{AFB5DA4E-366B-474f-84EB-99F835D3DAF3}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:72", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-033 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall provide spares, tools and consumables for all introduced systems and infrastructure", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA267.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5194", "0", "", "Class0","{A2E51F09-D40D-419d-B1F9-9F749E128CAD}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:73", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-034 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall provide the capability for Nominated Staff and required equipment to access required areas to perform Maintenance activities", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA268.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5195", "0", "", "Class0","{8CCB382D-F378-4ae9-98EB-F50F74B5C403}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:74", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-035 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall enable the storage and management of spares for the proposed system.", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA269.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5196", "0", "", "Class0","{EB70CFA5-0D6A-498a-9CE0-19F30045C893}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:75", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-055 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall minimise the risks of human error escalating to incidents and accidents SFAIRP", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA270.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5197", "0", "", "Class0","{CFEEB76F-E9D7-4f36-B464-705CDB8B550B}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:76", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-056 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall meet the anthropometric requirements of the 5th to 95th percentile of User", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA271.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5198", "0", "", "Class0","{2B7310D4-0AF6-4d35-8817-305C1BDF9E6F}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:77", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-057 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall not overload the cognitive capacity of the User", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA272.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5199", "0", "", "Class0","{1C8FBF7A-EFEB-4eb2-97A2-1625488B0805}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:78", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-058 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall allow access to both internal and external Emergency Services", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA273.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5200", "0", "", "Class0","{B718E989-5A6B-4a23-BFFD-B495EAA8EE24}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:79", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-059 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall demonstrate elmination Safety Risks so far as is reasonably practicable (SFAIRP)", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA274.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5201", "0", "", "Class0","{684850F2-33B1-42a2-8187-9C3290B82856}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:80", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-060 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall ensure safe operation during inter-running of BEL and Diesel Locomotives", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA275.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5202", "0", "", "Class0","{7FF57E15-E94A-448c-BDFA-3A98FF5AF38D}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:81", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-061 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall demonstrate maintenance activities can be conducted in a safe manner, so far as is reasonably practicable (SFAIRP)", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA276.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5203", "0", "", "Class0","{FCBC010D-606B-4e39-8EF6-B49F6C3A8FC2}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:82", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-069 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall be recoverable from Major Environmental Events", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA277.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5204", "0", "", "Class0","{D7E7E4F1-783A-41e0-8667-D6F60C3AB8EE}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:83", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-070 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall meet desired performance levels supporting 192Mtpa running, whilst in Abnormal or Degraded Modes.", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA278.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5205", "0", "", "Class0","{4B13CA56-383B-4e54-902F-E64D2FCE0D12}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:84", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-073 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall evaluate the compatibility and susceptibility of Electro-Magnetic Interference (EMI).", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA279.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5207", "0", "", "Class0","{B2BCFE6B-10ED-40db-9034-517B71EAEB68}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:85", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-074 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall provide Signalling Immunisation of the railway signalling system allowing for compatibility with new BEL and OLE systems.", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA280.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5208", "0", "", "Class0","{93F478C4-BE86-4bf8-8739-7BD5310375DA}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:86", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-075 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall not adversely impact the existing infrastructure through introduction of electrification to the system.", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA281.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5209", "0", "", "Class0","{548D6DD3-9CBC-4b18-B9A8-76CFDF2BC8D7}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:87", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-076 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall minimise EMI/EMC risks to all assets, Nominated Staff and public during operation and maintenance activities.", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA282.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5210", "0", "", "Class0","{F6B3122C-CBDB-4a73-BC1B-B32857E92E67}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:88", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-078 The Rail Decarbonisation System BEL vehicles shall have a Service Life of XX years (Same as the DEL)", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA283.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5211", "0", "", "Class0","{525AB73F-14A7-43cb-85B4-98DF1CBB2954}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:89", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-079 The Rail Decarbonisation System BEL Battery shall have a Service Life of XX years", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA284.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5212", "0", "", "Class0","{CEB6EB0D-AA64-4f34-A84F-FC65CC379F09}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:90", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-080 The Rail Decarbonisation System structural foundations shall have a Design Life of 100<br />years.", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA285.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5213", "0", "", "Class0","{66B77564-8A3B-4b06-B153-64101C472141}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:91", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-081 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall be supportable throughout the economic life", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA286.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5214", "0", "", "Class0","{D479FFD6-F93F-4d89-8B02-026EBBDF8206}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:92", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-082 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall accommodate future mine line changes to the network", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA287.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5215", "0", "", "Class0","{BABAEDB8-3855-4818-B922-453F806AD38F}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:93", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-083 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall remove all wayside assets rendered redundant by the implementation of the proposed solution", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA288.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5216", "0", "", "Class0","{D2A6DCC8-AEC9-4607-B9D7-E58350CBE57E}");
tocTab[tocTab.length] = new Array("0.3.3.1:94", "", "«ArchiMate_Requirement» RDP-BRS-084 The Rail Decarbonisation System shall safely decommission the Diesel Locomotive fleet at the end of their life, so far as is reasonably practicable (SFAIRP)", "EARoot/EA3/EA3/EA1/EA289.-1", "9F0DDA8A-5_ArchiMate_Requirement.png", "E5217", "0", "", "Class0","{ACC95314-7023-4ebb-AABC-240D6755E5B8}");
